Guide to the Lawrence Klein Papers, 1950s-2010 RL.00786
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Lawrence Klein papers
1950s-2010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Klein, Lawrence R. (Lawrence Robert), 1920-2013
RL.00786
52.5 Linear Feet 40,000 items
Nobel-prize winning economist and professor at the University of Pennsylvania's Wharton School. Collection includes Klein's correspondence, writings and drafts, economic research and subject files, organizational papers, and dissertations from Klein's many students. Contains significant amount of material from Project LINK, particularly from the late 1960s. Audiovisual recordings of the first LINK conference in 1969 will require reformatting prior to use. Also includes files from Klein's presidency of the National Academy of Science, his professorship at the University of Pennsylvania's Wharton School, and printouts from early economic computer programs and experiments.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Research Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Lawrence Klein Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1986 and 2011.
Biographical Note
Lawrence Robert Klein (1920-2013) was an American economist born in Omaha, Nebraska. He died at age 93 on October 20, 2013 in Galdwyne, Pennsylvania. Much of his work involved building macroeconometric models for economic forecasting. He earned his undergraduate degree at the University of California, Berkeley, in 1942, and studied under economist Paul Samuelson at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), completing his Ph.D. in 1944. In November 1944, Klein was recruited at the Cowles Commission as research associate to work on the construction of a macroeconometric model of the US economy. In the following years, he worked at the National Bureau of Economic Research, the Survey Research Center of the University of Michigan, and the Institute of Statistics at the University of Oxford, before accepting a position at the University of Pennsylvania in 1958. In 1968, he became the Benjamin Franklin Professor of Economics and Finance at the Wharton School. Klein received the John Bates Clark Medal in 1959, while, in 1980, he was awarded the Sveriges Riksbank Prize in Economic Sciences in Memory of Alfred Nobel.
With the purpose of providing a scientific tool for policy analysis and economic planning, Klein led and participated in various projects to build large-scale macroeconometric models in several countries. Some of these important projects were the Wharton School models, the SSRC-Brookings model, and the multinational Project LINK. Throughout his life, Klein also built a vast international network of collaborators, visiting and working with economists from all around the world since the late 1940s. In these early years Klein went several times to Norway, the Netherlands, and the United Kingdom, where he met with Ragnar Frisch, Jan Tinbergen, and Richard Stone among many others. Later on, during the 1960s, 1970s and 1980s, Klein continued his international activity, visiting not only European countries, but also establishing important relations with economists in Japan, China, Australia, Israel, and Mexico among other countries. Klein’s earlier enthusiasm about Marxist theory was later reflected in his special interest on the possibilities of building large-scale macroeconometric models of Soviet countries. He and his wife, Sonia, had four children.
Collection Overview
The collection includes Klein's correspondence, writings and drafts, economic research and subject files, organizational papers, and dissertations from Klein's many students. It contains significant amount of material from Project LINK, particularly from the late 1960s. Audiovisual recordings of the first LINK conference in 1969 will require reformatting prior to use. Also included are files from Klein's presidency of the National Academy of Science, his professorship at the University of Pennsylvania's Wharton School, and printouts from early economic computer programs and experiments.
The Dissertations series includes copies and drafts of dissertations and theses written by Klein's students and advisees during his tenure at the University of Pennsylvania. They are arranged in alphabetical order by the author's name.
The Subjects, Organizations, and Research series includes subject files and materials on various publications, research topics, projects, and organizations with which Klein worked. This series includes many materials from his career at the University of Pennsylvania, including teaching materials and committee information, as well as his presidency of the National Academy of Sciences. It has been arranged alphabetically by folder title.
The Project LINK series contains records related to that project, for which Klein served as principal investigator along with Bert Hickman, Rudolf Rhomberg, and Aaron Gordon. Included are materials from various meetings, research materials, and reports.
The Computer Printouts series contains computer printouts from an unknown project, possibly Project LINK, dating from the early 1980s.
The Correspondence series contains letters, memos, and faxes received or written by Klein. Much of the correspondence was exchanged with colleagues in the field of economics, and reflects collaborative research endeavors. Arranged loosely by correspondent within each year. Not every year has incoming correspondence.
Writings by Klein includes papers and speeches written by Lawrence Klein for journals, newspapers, editorials, and congressional testimony.
Writings by Others includes non-dissertation writings on economics collected by Klein for his own research or interest.
Audiovisual Materials contains audio recordings of the first worldwide Project LINK conference in 1969. This material will need to be reformatted prior to use.
There is also a small amount of Unsorted Miscellaneous material.
In addition, a small amount of electronic media has been removed from the collection and transferred to Duke's server. Please contact Research Services for access to this material.
Audiovisual materials; Economic history; Macroeconomics; Nobel Prize winners; Economics; Econometric models; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.); Klein, Lawrence R. (Lawrence Robert), 1920-2013; Wharton School; University of Pennsylvania. Dept. of Economics; Project Link
- Dissertations, 1960s-2000, 14 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes dissertations and drafts from Klein's students and other advisees, ranging in date from the late 1960s through 2000. Arranged alphabetically by author's name in record storage cartons, unless otherwise noted.
  - A-Be (Box 1)
  - Be-Broo (Box 2)
  - Brow-Fin (Box 3)
  - Fitz-Ham (Box 4)
  - Har-Hyun (Box 5)
  - Hyun-Mar (Box 6)
  - Mar-Mon (Box 7)
  - Mon-Par (Box 8)
  - Pir-Row (Box 9)
  - Row-Ste (Box 10)
  - Swa-Untitled (Box 11)
  - Untitled-Wei (Box 12)
  - Wei-Yeh, 1/2 size box (Box 13)
  - Yoo-Z and loose pages, 1/2 size box (Box 14)
- Subjects, Organizations, and Research, 1963-1991, 6 boxes
  Contains subject files on various publications, economic research topics, and projects. Also contains organizational papers, including materials from Klein's presidency at the National Academy of Science, his work with the National Science Foundation, and his professorship at the University of Pennsylvania. Project LINK formed such a substantial portion of the materials that it is a separate series. Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject in record storage cartons.
  - Academy of Science, 1972 (Box 15)
  - AEA, 1966-1972, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - American Telephone and Telegraph, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Australia, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Brookings Institute, 1968-1971 (Box 15)
  - Business Week, 1969-1970, 1982, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Canada Council, 1968-1971 (Box 15)
  - Coal, 4 folders (Box 15)
  - DuPont - Brazil (Box 15)
  - Econometric Society, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Federal Reserve Price Committee (Box 15)
  - Flow of Funds, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Food and Finance Committee mailing lists (Box 15)
  - Ford Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 15)
  - Harrison, Bennett (University of Maryland), 1968-1971 (Box 15)
  - IBM, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Independence Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Institute of Social and Economic Research, 1968 (Box 15)
  - International Cooperation and Stabilization Policies Symposium, no date (Box 15)
  - International Economic Review, 1970-1973 (Box 15)
  - International Monetary Fund, 1968-1971 (Box 15)
  - Japan Economic Research Center, 1972 (Box 15)
  - MacMillan, 1968-1972 (Box 16)
  - Markham, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Maurice Falk Institute, Jerusalem, 1969-1972 (Box 16)
  - Mexico, 1970-1972 (Box 16)
  - National Academy of Science
    - Finance Committee Papers, 1976-1979, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Nomination/election forms, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Chairman materials, 1985-1991, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Class membership, 1987-1989, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Membership nominations, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Ballots, 1989, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Membership selections, 1989-1990 (Box 16)
    - Nomination proposals, supporting materials, 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Ballots, 1990, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Membership committees, 1991 (Box 16)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1989-1992, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - National Research Council, 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - National Science Foundation
    - Summer Research Institute application, 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Summer Research Institute application, 1971, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Proposal, 1972, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 17)
    - NSF/CNRS Papers, 1976-1978 (Box 17)
    - NSF/CNRS Seminar, 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Negative Income Tax, 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Peace Research, 1969-1971 (Box 17)
  - Prentice Hall, 1971-1973 (Box 17)
  - Project "Hydra" Klausner, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Rubber, 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Russian Meetings, 1970 (Box 17)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1968-1970 (Box 17)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1971, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Survey Research Center, University of Michigan, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Technical report: Robust Non-Linear Data Smoothing, by Paul F. Velleman, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Tin, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Treasury Study, 1967-1969 (Box 18)
  - Wharton E.F.A., 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Vitae, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Vienna, 1970 (Institute for Advanced Studies) (Box 18)
  - University of Massachusetts, 1966-1971, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - University of Pennsylvania
    - Academic Calendar, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
    - Academic Planning Committee, 1972, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Benjamin Franklin University Professors, 1963-1972, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Bills, invoices, etc (Box 18)
    - Budget Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
    - Budget Committee, 1972 (Box 19)
    - Committee on Economic History (Box 19)
    - Committee on Education Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    - Committee on Faculty Affairs, 1971 (Box 19)
    - Committee on University-State Relations, 1962-1966 (Box 19)
    - Committee to appoint a Dean for the Graduate School, 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Computer Center reports, 1968-1972, 5 folders (Box 19)
    - Computer numbers (Box 19)
    - Company Contributions to Forecasting Unit (Box 19)
    - Curriculum (Box 19)
    - Dean of Law School Committee, 1969 (Box 19)
    - Development Commission (Box 19)
    - Econometric Society meeting (Box 19)
    - Econometric Unit, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Economics Department, 1968-1970 (Box 19)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 19)
    - Fels Institute of Local and State Government (Box 19)
    - Financial Statements, ER (Box 19)
    - Investment Banking Chair (Box 19)
    - Librarian search, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
    - Personnel Committee (Box 19)
    - Provost Search Committee, 1970 (Box 19)
    - Search for University of Pennsylvania Athletic Director, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Student recommendations, 1970-1973 (Box 19)
    - Sujan, 1970 (Box 19)
    - Summer employment (Box 19)
    - University Committee on Statistics Professors, 1963 (Box 19)
    - University Planning Committee, 1965-1972 (Box 19)
  - Virginia State College, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Wharton E.F.A., 1968-1971 and no date, 8 folders (Box 20)
  - Wharton Quarterly, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
- Project LINK, 1950-1996, 2 boxes
  Contains materials on Project LINK, an international research project integrating various national econometric models into a global econometric model. (About Project LINK, UN DESA, accessed November 30, 2011, http://www.un.org/en/development/desa/policy/proj_link/index.shtml). Klein served as one of the principal investigators for this project. Tapes of the first worldwide Project LINK meeting can be found in the A/V for Project LINK, 1969 series.
  - Annual Meeting, Newport, RI, 1971, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Annual Meeting, Vienna, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Australia, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
  - Austria, 1969-1971 (Box 20)
  - Belgium Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 20)
  - Canada, 1968-1970 (Box 20)
  - European Meeting (Paris), 1968 (Box 20)
  - France (Box 20)
  - General correspondence and reports, 1968-1971, 9 folders (Box 20)
  - General correspondence and reports, 1968-1973, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Germany (Box 21)
  - International Monetary Fund, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Haley, 1968-1970 (Box 21)
  - Japan, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - London meetings, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Meeting participants lists, 1987-1996, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Mini-LINK exercises, 1970s (Box 21)
  - Regional models, 1950-1970 (Box 21)
  - Research, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Sweden, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - UNCTAD models, 1968-1970, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - U.K., 1968-1970 (Box 21)
  - World meeting prep, 1971-1973 (Box 21)
  - World meeting report, 1972 (Box 21)
  - World Outlook, 1983 (Box 21)
- Computer printouts, 1970s-1983, 3 boxes
  - Printouts (Box 22)
  - Printouts (Box 23)
  - Printouts (Box 24)
- Correspondence, 1968-2010; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Includes letters, memos, faxes, etc. Years are generally arranged alphabetically by first letter of correspondents' surnames. Outgoing correspondence from 1987 is arranged chronologically in record storage cartons. Some additional correspondence can be found in the Subjects, Organizations, and Research and Project LINK series.
  - Correspondence A-Z, 1968 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence A-B, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence C-D, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence E-F, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence J-L, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence M-O, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence R-S, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence T-V, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence W-Z, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence A-B, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence C-D, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence E-F, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence G-I, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence J-L, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence M-O, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence P-Q, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence R-S, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence W-Z, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence A-B, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence C-D, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence E-F, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence G-I, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence J-L, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence M-O, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence P-Q, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence R-S, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence T-V, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence W-Z, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence A-B, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence C-D, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence E-G, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence H-J, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence K-L, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence M-O, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence P-R, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence S-T, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence U-Z, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence A-Z, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence A-Z ("Dead letter file"), 1974 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence I, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence M, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence A, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence B, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence D, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence F, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence G, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence I, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence J, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence K, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence L, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence M, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence N, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence O, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence P, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence R, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence S, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence T, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence U-V, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence W, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence Y-Z, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 26)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1987 (Jan-March) (Box 27)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1987 (April-August) (Box 27)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1987 (August-December) (Box 27)
  - Correspondence A, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence B, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence C, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence D-F, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence G, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence H, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence I-J, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence K, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence L, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence M-O, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence P, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence R, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence S, part 1, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence S, part 2, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence T, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence U-Z, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence A, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence B, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence C, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence D, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence E-F, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence G, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence H, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence I-F, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence K, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence L, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence M, part 1, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence M, part 2, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence N, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence O-P, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence R, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence S, part 1, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence S, part 2, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence S, part 3, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence T, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence U-V, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence W-Z, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence A, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence B, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence C, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence D, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence E-F, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence G, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence H, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence I-J, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence K, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence L, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence M, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence N, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence O-P, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence Q-R, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence S, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence T, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence U-V, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence W-Z, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence A, 1992 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence B, 1992 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence C, 1992 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence D-E, 1992 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence F-G, 1992 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence H, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence I-J, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence K, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence L, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence M, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence N-O, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence P-Q, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence R, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence S, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence T, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence U-V, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence W-Z, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence A, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence B, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence C, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence D-E, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence F-G, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence H-I, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence J-K, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence L, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence M-N, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence P-Q, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence R-S, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence T-V, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence W, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence Y-Z, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence A-B, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence C, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence D-E, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence F-G, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence H, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence I, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence J-L, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1995 (Box 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence Jan-Mar, 1996 (Box 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence April-May, 1996 (Box 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence Nov-Jan, 1996-1997 (Box 30)
  - Outgoing Correspondence October, 2010 (Box 30)
- Writings, 1969-1998 and undated; 1
  - America's Competitive Position, undated (Box 30)
  - Business Forecasting, undated (Box 30)
  - Catching Up with US, undated (Box 30)
  - Simulation of an Autonomatic Stabilization Program in the 1975 Recession, undated (Box 30)
  - Contains Lawrence Klein's Comments on Michael Wachter's article for the Wharton Quarterly, undated (Box 30)
  - The Analytic Calculation of the Variances of Forecasts of General Econometric Structural Models, undated (Box 30)
  - Comments on several papers, undated (Box 30)
  - A Comparison of Eleven Econometric models of the United States, undated (Box 30)
  - Disturbances to the International Economy, undated (Box 30)
  - Dynamic Analysis of Economic Systems, undated (Box 30)
  - Dynamic Properties of Nonlinear Econometric Models, undated (Box 30)
  - Econometrics, undated (Box 30)
  - Early Warning Signals of Inflation, undated (Box 30)
  - Econometric Models, undated (Box 30)
  - Econometric Models, undated (Box 30)
  - Econometric Models: Empirical Application, History, undated (Box 30)
  - Economic Conditions and the Outlook for the United States, undated (Box 30)
  - The Economic Module, undated (Box 30)
  - The Economic Outlook for Japan, undated (Box 30)
  - Anticipations Variables in Macroeconometric Models, 1971 (Box 30)
  - A Suggestion for Estimation of the Linear Expenditure System, 1972 (Box 30)
  - The State of the Monetarist Debate, 1973 (Box 30)
  - America's First University, 1973 September (Box 30)
  - Capacity Utilization-Concept, Measurement, and Recent Estimates, 1973 November (Box 30)
  - Econometrics of Inlfation, 1965-74. A Review of the Decade, 1974 (Box 30)
  - Economic Consequences of the ADL Capital Need Program, 1974 August (Box 30)
  - Business Cycle Modeling without much a priori Economic Theory, 1975 November (Box 30)
  - Computer Modeling of Macroeconomic Systems: The State of the Art, 1975 December (Box 30)
  - The Basic Materials Situation and a Narional Policy, 1975/76 (Box 30)
  - The Economic Outlook, 1976 (Box 30)
  - Econometric Modeling for State and Local Policy, 1976 March (Box 30)
  - The Economic Module in Global Modeling, 1976 April (Box 30)
  - The Future of the World Economy, 1976 June (Box 30)
  - Econometric Model Building at the Regional Level, 1976 October (Box 30)
  - The Carter Factor, 1977 January (Box 30)
  - Econometric Specification for OECD Countries (for Spain), 1977 June (Box 30)
  - Computer Modeling of Macroeconomic Systems: The State of the Art, 1977 September (Box 30)
  - An Overview of the Objectives and Framework of Seasonal Adjustment, 1977 October (Box 30)
  - Coordination of International Fiscal Policies and Exchange rate Revaluations, 1978 January (Box 30)